mkhoj.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy Policy | InMobi

##  Last Updated: July 27, 2011

This Privacy Policy explains how information is collected and utilized by InMobi Pte Ltd ("InMobi" or "we", "us", "our"), its subsidiaries and affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy applies to the InMobi website at www.inMobi.com (the "Site"). For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is the UK branch of InMobi Pte Ltd of The Heals Building, 22 Torrington Place, London WC1E 7HJ, while the data processor is InMobi Pte Ltd., UOB Plaza 1, 36th Floor 80, Raffles Place, Singapore.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your and your consumers (“Consumers”) data and how we will treat it. 

InMobi is committed to respecting and protecting privacy for its publishers, advertisers, developers, and their Consumers. This Privacy Policy describes our practices with respect to you, your company's, or your Consumers' data. For each element of data we collect, this Privacy Policy (referred to below as the "Policy") describes:

  * What data we collect.
  * How we use such data.
  * How we protect the data.
  * How you can change it or delete the data.

The Policy covers all aspects of our mobile advertising business, including:

  * Publishers and developers who are partnering with us to deliver services based on mobile advertising.
  * Advertisers and developers who are advertising goods and services through our network.
  * Interested parties visiting our website to access information or content.

By partnering with us as a publisher, advertising through our network, or visiting the site and/or using InMobi's services, you agree to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of the Policy, you should not access the Site or otherwise use the InMobi's services.

InMobi divides data into four areas: 1) account information that you provide to us and is required for us to conduct business with you. 2) anonymous or aggregated information that we collect to improve our product on your behalf. 3) UDID, which is recognized by us as sensitive information and handled separately; and 4) personally identifiable information.

## 1\. What personally identifiable information do we collect?

Personally identifiable information (referred to as "PII") is the most important category of data and we are committed to protecting this information and following best practices in this area. We view PII during the ad serving process (e.g. MSISDN), but do not collect it. We do collect your PII (and not that of any Consumers) during the account sign up process, but only with explicit permission from you.

## 2\. We reference MSISDN as "seen" during the ad serving process, but not collected. Here is what we mean?

MSISDN is sometimes observed during the ad serving process. This information, which can be linked to a consumer's actual phone number, is often included in the header information coming from the consumer's phone during the ad serving process. This header information is the source of anonymous data about the device and crucial to ad performance. Essentially, MSISDN is a by-product of collecting anonymous data about the handset used for targeting and reporting purposes. When viewed, we instantaneously encrypt it with a one-way irretrievable hash encryption at the point of receipt, using industry standard encryption technology. The process nullifies its PII properties and offers the most robust protection available. We do not collect or use MSISDN in our business. We do not link any other data to MSISDN. We do not share MSISDN (even after the one-way hash encryption process) with any third party.

## 3\. What account information do we collect?

We collect personal account information that you provide including, but not limited to, name, address, email, phone number, twitter or social network profiles IDs, company name, and geography. This information is provided by you with your explicit permission as a means to conducting business with InMobi. No such information of the Consumer is collected by us.

## 4\. How do we use this account information?

This information is used to communicate with you, conduct businesses with you including reporting and payment, to provide you access to your account or information, and to generally improve your experience with our product and services.

## 5\. How is your account information protected?

The personal account information you provide is stored in a secure fashion, behind a firewall, in one of our servers in either the US, Ireland, Japan, or India. It is stored behind multiple levels of authorization (refer Section 16 _"Security"_ ) and access to this information is limited to InMobi employees or third party service providers on a need to know basis only and for the purposes of managing your account. All our employees and third party subcontractors are bound by appropriate confidentiality obligations, in line with the terms of this provision. This information is only used to conduct business with you. We reserve the right to transfer this information as necessary within the confines of our firewall and server network or the protected server networks of our third party subcontractors with appropriate industry standard protection measures and authorizations. For clarity, any third party subcontractors use such information solely to provide services to us and for no other purpose. All third party subcontractors are mandated to return or destroy all our information upon completion of assignment. We also reserve the right to expand our server network to additional countries as necessary.

## 6\. How can you change or delete your account information?

You can edit or delete your personal information by logging into your account at our website, [www.inmobi.com](http://www.inmobi.com/) and editing the data.

## 7\. What anonymous or aggregated information do we collect?

We collect anonymous or aggregated information from our business partners, their Consumers, third parties, and site visitors. Such information is important for the proper performance of our services and if not collected, some portions of our services may not perform appropriately. This information includes, but is not limited to, blind cookies that allow us to identify site visitors in an anonymous manner, technical information about the handset (e.g. make, model, OS) general demographic data (e.g. age, gender), location information (e.g. country, zip code, postal code, ISP), content type (e.g. games, finance, entertainment, news & information), ad type (e.g. text, image, automotive, travel, gaming), URL information of the ad being served, and information from advertisers about the post-click activity of the ads we serve. Given the harmless nature of this information and its benefits to our clients, we reserve the right to enhance or add anonymous or aggregated information at any time without notice.

## 8\. How do we use this anonymous or aggregated information?

We use anonymous or aggregated information from 3rd party business partners and site visitors to enhance our ad serving, offer publisher ad filters and controls, provide general reporting capabilities, and personalize the site experience at [www.inmobi.com](http://www.inmobi.com/). More specifically, the data is used to either provide pre-buy targeting options for advertisers, filtering options for publishers to manage ads appearing on their sites, enhance real time post ad impression delivery targeting using our Advertiser ROI Tracking Technology called AdROIt, and enhance services and reporting broadly. This information is not linked to your account information or PII. We reserve the right to share this information with third parties to improve our product or services. We do not send any unsolicited messages or other spam to consumers.

## 9\. How is this anonymous or aggregated information protected?

Anonymous or aggregated information is stored in a secure fashion, behind a firewall, in one of our servers in either the US, Ireland, Japan, or India (refer Section 16 _"Security"_ ). Any Consumer information, of the nature referred above, from Europe or North America is stored in Ireland or in the United States. No personally identifiable information from any Consumer is collected, retained or used. All anonymous or aggregated information is stored behind multiple levels of authorization and access to this information is limited to InMobi employees or third party service providers on a need to know basis only and for the purposes of managing your account. All our employees and third party subcontractors are bound by appropriate confidentiality obligations, in line with the terms of this provision. This information is used for the purpose of improving and enhancing our products and services. We reserve the right to transfer this information as necessary within the confines of our firewall and server network or the protected server networks of our third party subcontractors with appropriate industry standard protection measures and authorizations. For clarity, any third party subcontractors use such information solely to provide services to us and for no other purpose. All third party subcontractors are mandated to return or destroy all our information upon completion of assignment. We also reserve the right to expand our server network to additional countries as necessary.

## 10\. How can you change or delete anonymous or aggregated information?

This information is not and will not be linked to the personal information you provided or the personally identifiable information we collect. Therefore it is not possible, nor is it necessary, to edit or delete the data.

## 11\. What you must indicate in your privacy policy?

You shall clearly indicate in your privacy policy that you use third parties, who may collect anonymous information about Consumers visits to your websites or applications using cookies and Consumers interaction with your products and services and also UDID's. The use of cookies is an industry standard technology used by most major web sites and is explained below, under the Section 14 titled "Cookies".  
You shall mention the information that may be collected by such third parties used by you, as indicated under the Section 7 _"What anonymous or aggregated information do we collect?"_ and Section 12 _"Do you collect and use UDID?"_ You should also inform Consumers that no personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process, (in particular that the third parties used by you do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the Consumers). You should inform the Consumers about the use and protection of such anonymous or aggregated information and UDID information in accordance with the Section 8 titled _"How do we use this anonymous or aggregated information?"_ , Section 9 _"How is this anonymous or aggregated information protected?"_ , Section 12 _"Do you collect and use UDID?"_ and Section 13 _"How is the UDID information protected?"_.

## 12\. Do you collect and use UDID?

We collect the UDID of Consumers, if observed during the ad serving process. This information, which can be linked to a Consumer's actual mobile device, is often included in the header information coming from the Consumer's phone during the ad serving process. This header information is the source of anonymous data about the device crucial to ad performance. Essentially, UDID is a by-product of collecting anonymous data about the handset used for targeting and reporting purposes. When received, we instantaneously encrypt it using a one-way hash encryption. The process completely nullifies its PII properties. We use such hashed UDID strings on an aggregate basis to improve our service offerings in our business to you and Consumers, similar to how we use anonymous and aggregated information. We never provide any UDID in unhashed form to any 3rd party. We also share hashed UDID data with 3rd party service providers, if needed, who are bound by strict confidentiality obligations solely to perform services for us. To reiterate, any hashed UDID data is hashed using industry standard one-way hashing techniques such that the hashed data is irretrievable and not 'personally identifiable', as explained in the next section. To opt out, please click Opt Out.

## 13\. How is this UDID information protected?

When received, we instantaneously encrypt it using a one-way hash encryption. Once encrypted, there is no way to decrypt it and get the original UDID. The process completely nullifies its PII properties and offers the most robust consumer protection approach possible.

## 14\. Cookies

When you prepare to log-on to this Site or use our services, our server may automatically recognize your or Consumer's mobile phone browser alphanumeric identifiers that is also known as a "cookie". We may set one or more cookies in your or Consumer's mobile phone browser when you visit the Site or use our services. InMobi is not involved in any targeted advertising and does not use any cookies for behavioral targeting. InMobi's use of cookies is restricted to collecting anonymous or aggregated information (as indicated above) solely for performing services for You.

## 15\. Data Retention

We shall retain your information and any other data for only as long as it is necessary.

## 16\. Security

We have various electronic, procedural and physical security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information, or any accidental loss, destruction or damage to data, if the same is under our control. We take every precaution to protect our users’ information. When you submit your information via our website, your information is protected through our security systems. You agree to be responsible to protect the security of your username and password and other registration details. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to [helpdesk@inmobi.com](mailto:helpdesk@inmobi.com) or reach us at +91 (80) 6583 4445.

## 17\. Links

We may create links to other websites. You are requested to be aware that we do not provide any personally identifiable information to such other websites and that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites as those may have different privacy policies and terms of use and are not associated with us. You agree that we cannot control these links and we shall not be responsible for any use of such websites.

## 18\. Modification

We reserve the right to amend this policy at any time. The policies, as and how modified, shall be updated on our website ([www.inmobi.com](http://www.inmobi.com/)) and the same shall be notified on the website.

## 19\. Contacts

In case, You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [helpdesk@inmobi.com](mailto:helpdesk@inmobi.com) or at the following Customer Care contact no. +91 (80) 6583 4445 **between 9:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m./ 24x7**.
